TOMAS JONG



Stockholm, Sweden



tom.jon0129@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a senior full stack developer with 10 years of experience.

So far I participated in more than 30+ projects successfully and I have rich experience in vast area.

Development is my life and I used to satisfy all the requirements coming from the clients and users.

As a problem solver, I like to challenge coding and I have a good team spirt.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Jul. 2019 - Nov. 2021 Singapore

Full Stack Engineer, Enjin.io

Enjin offers a suite of integrated products that make nonfungible tokens (NFTs) easy for individuals, businesses, and developers.

I was responsible for developing the frontend part mainly but I worked as a full stack developer.

- Figma to HTML/CSS
- · Worked with Javascript frameworks and libraries
- Participated in API Development

Mar. 2016 - May. 2019 United States

Senior Frontend Developer, Fortnite

Fortnite is a free-to-play Battle Royale game with numerous game modes for every type of game player. Watch a concert, build an island or fight.

I was responsible for developing the frontend parts.

- Sketch to React
- Add animation
- API Integration
- Code Optimization

Jun. 2013 – Mar. 2016 United States

Full Stack Engineer, Red Apple Interactive Pharmacy

Red Apple Interactive Pharmacy is a next generation retail pharmacy with a goal of advancing and broadening the delivery of retail health in an interactive way.

I worked as a full stack engineer.

- App Development with Ionic
- Website Development with pure PHP and vanilla Javascript
- jQuery Mobile Development

EDUCATION

Mar. 2013

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

• University of Kalmar - Kalmar

SKILLS

React/Next Expert **Vue/Nuxt** Expert **Angular** Expert Node.js Expert **React Native, Vue Native** Expert Javascript/Typescript Expert **PHP & PHP Frameworks** Expert MySQL, MongoDB, Firebase, etc Expert Git Expert **Django/Python** Experienced **Dev Ops** Experienced Third API Integration (Paypal, Stripe, Twilio, Experienced **GraphQL**, etc)